

Igor Freitas Couto

30 years, Juiz de Fora MG, Brazil igor.fcouto@gmail.com +55 32 99135-6461

github.com/igor-couto (7) linkedin.com/in/igor-fcouto in

PROFILE

Full-Stack Developer with 5 years of experience in .NET technologies and software architecture. Dedicated to meeting daily work challenges and committed to not only delivering quality code but also creating software that positively impacts the company and its customers. Adheres to Agile principles and best practices.

SKILLS

- C# (.NET Core)

- Unit testing
- Functional Testing
 SQL Server
- Angular
 JavaScript
 TypeScript
 Functional Testing
 SQL Server
 MongoDB
 Redis
- Git & GitFlow Design Patterns Dapper
- Postgres

- HTML5 e CSS Clean Code Entity Framework

- Azure Cloud • UML
- AWS Cloud Adobe Photoshop
- Docker • Figma
 - Blender 3D CI/CD

WORK EXPERIENCE

Lambda3 Consulting — Full Time Software Developer OCTOBER 2020 — PRESENT

Worked on projects aligned with Agile philosophy. Participated in the development of a chat and customer service system for one of the main retail chains in Brazil, leading to increased market share, especially during the pandemic. Developed a banking account system for a company in the loyalty segment, using points redeemable through cashback. For a fast-growing fintech company, created an integration system that generated bank slips based on customer orders.

Delage Logistics & Supply Chain — Full Time Systems Analyst MARCH 2018 — OCTOBER 2020

Developed a Warehouse Management System and related logistics software. Conducted client visits for product sales and deployments in Brazil and Argentina. Designed and implemented system interfaces for third-party integration (ERPs and automation), and maintained legacy systems. Created APIs and Windows Services.

Prime System Technical Courses — Part Time Teacher MARCH 2017 — MARCH 2018

Taught Introduction to Programming with C#, Unity Game Engine, and 3D modeling.

EDUCATION

Federal University of Juiz de Fora — Bachelor of Information Systems

Made significant contributions to academic activities prior to leaving the program in 2018:

- Member of junior enterprise CODE
- Member of Group for Computer Graphics, Image and Vision
- Member of Computer Science Tutorial Education Group where I participated in the development of EducAR Quadrics and LocalizAR UFJF apps
- Course taught to 40 students about 3D modeling
- Co-author of two academic articles [1] [2]

LANGUAGES

Portuguese English Spanish Native Speaker from Brazil **Professional Working Proficiency Limited Working Proficiency**